In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
I beseech anyone who can stop
the march of Tudor's black devils...
D-Don't break up your formation!
Encircle him!
T-They are...
The Band of the Hawk!
The Grim Reapers of the Battlefield
led by the White Hawk, Griffith!
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
A Wind of Swords
R-Retreat, retreat!
Y-Your Majesty!
Captain! Captain Guts!
It was amazing, Captain!
You took them in one charge!
That was something else!
Nothing less from our raider commander!
You're our boss, all right!
You did a good job too...
Sorry, I got a little carried away.
No need to apologize.
We get to brag about our
commander to everyone else!
He's right!
Now let's have a drink to celebrate!
Captain Guts!
Big sister Casca...
Commander Casca!
We need to talk.
Can I have your ear for a minute, Captain Guts?
Hey, start without me.
I'll catch up.
What's going on?
They're going to start arguing again.
It's probably over
the captain's lone charge into battle.
What did you think you were doing?
About what?
Don't give me that!
Our plan was to support
the main force's charge...
...while our companies each cover
a flank and contain the enemy attack.
Despite your success...
...you ruined our battle plans, charging
alone into the center of the enemy!
Who do you think you are, some hero?
Even though we were lucky this time...
Your selfish actions could put all of
the Band of the Hawk in real danger!
Try to keep your position in mind sometimes!
I apologize!
I'll be careful in the future.
You always say that!
You're always insincere.
You just repeat the same thing...
The fact is you haven't changed at all
from who you were three years ago...
...when you first sunk your teeth into Griffith.
All you care about
is swinging your sword in battle.
You don't care at all about your men.
You're just a mad dog!
Say that again...
Say that again if you dare!
Why don't you two calm down now?
Griffith!
Casca, I will give Guts some advice...
Griffith, you're too soft on him.
You go through too much
trouble for him, sister Casca.
He's Griffith's favorite pet.
You just end up taking all
the blame whenever you confront him.
Well, I'm willing to help
whenever you want to bump him off.
Sorry.
Damn it!
You two fight like cats and dogs.
Yet you've spent almost
three years in the same group.
I care about them...
In my own way, I do care about my men.
I'm not who I was in the past.
It takes me back...
...to three years ago.
You were wandering from battlefield to battlefield.
And we had a duel
that resulted in you joining us.
That duel was so much fun...
That is the way duels should be.
Come on now.
You will be the toast of tonight's drinking.
Griffith...
About today's battle...
I'm sorry.
I drew up my battle plans
with your tendencies in mind.
Not quarreling with some evil design...
Not straying from virtue...
Sacrifice thyself ceaselessly...
This is absolutely unheard of.
Render service for peace and security.
A mercenary granted knighthood...
What on Earth is the king thinking?
By the spirit of the kingdom of Midland...
But they were a great help.
The title of knight is bestowed on thee.
Nonsense!
They would be thieves without war.
Place thy flesh and heart in heaven.
Separate thyself from falsehood.
Nevertheless, their services on the...
...battlefield are necessary.
Uphold the law, know the subjects...
If we sit back now, we'll disappear.
Be valiant with due courtesy and fidelity...
They have no choice but
to acknowledge their ability.
Because we have continuously
distinguished ourselves in battle.
Right, Rickert?
It's farewell to the humble mercenary life.
We've been publicly
admitted into the regular army.
Watch your tongue
if you know where we are, Corkus.
We're in the middle of a ceremony.
From now on, our behavior
could reflect badly on Griffith.
There is no longer any excuse
to act like boorish mercenaries.
Okay, okay, I understand,
Commander Casca, ma'am.
She's tougher than my mom.
What was that?
Hey, we're at a ceremony!
Those commoners...
Wait a minute. He's not here again!
One hundred ninety-five...
One hundred ninety-six...
One hundred ninety-seven...
One hundred ninety-eight...
One hundred ninety-nine...
Two hundred!
Thanks for scouting, Judeau.
So what's going on
at the enemy's supply base?
Their defense focuses on this side,
so our information was correct.
It's not much of a force though.
If so, we should try
to outflank them or something.
No...
We attack them from the front.
But that's dangerous!
Our objective is to capture the enemy
supply base as soon as possible.
We could probably reach the armory
swiftly by attacking from behind...
However, we'd also draw
the garrison to the armory if we did.
In that case, it'd take more time
to completely occupy the fort.
I see...
To thin the fort's guard, we should
attack the front of the supply base.
Yes.
Additionally...
We'll deal with the armory as soon as possible.
Be extremely careful after breaking
through the fort's central gate.
So what's our formation?
First, Guts and Casca's companies
will attract the garrisons' attention.
The main company will ride into
the fort and break through the front.
I got it.
As soon as the preparations
are complete, we'll start the operation.
Oh boy...
Guts will end up snatching the credit again!
Hey, you want to argue with me?
Casca!
Griffith gave those orders!
We are no longer mercenaries.
Keep that in mind.
Look, if you go off on your own again...
...you will...
Guts!
I'm depending on you, Casca.
Why should I...
...I, the leader of the Blue Whale
Heavy Assault Knights, Sir Adon...
Why do I have to patrol this miserable
supply base and its armory?
Sir, it's because the Black Ram Heavy Cavalry...
...was crippled, so we were
installed here as a substitute.
Hush!
I know that!
It's beneath one of the glorious
Coborlwitz family to be in this mission.
Damn!
What is it?
Well, I see something...
Hey!
Commander Adon!
It's an enemy raid!
Don't be foolish!
Who on Earth would bother
to attack such a remote supply base?
W-What?
T-This is...
Don't fall back!
You son of a bitch!
C-Commander!
Shit!
He's doing it again!
Hold it, Guts!
Did you forget our duty?
Get out of my way!
Guts!
Griffith!
It's a trap!
Turn around!
What?
Retreat!
Retreat?
That can't be!
Hurry up, Corkus!
What the hell?
Take shelter!
That was my special fleeing technique, Bakuretsu Funsai!
It's been handed down through
the Coborlwitz family for 300 years!
B-But the fort... Our key supply base is...
Shut up!
Quit yapping!
Now withdraw the troops!
Is everyone all right?
I'm glad everyone is okay!
It's thanks to Guts.
But really, that explosion was something else!
All the spoils were destroyed.
It's no big deal.
We were able to achieve our objective
and damage the enemy supply base.
What are you talking about?
You are totally an amateur, kid.
Sorry I'm young!
What's bothering you?
Get to the point, if you have something to say!
It's not like you to hesitate!
Shut up!
I just...
I just want to say that your
actions in battle today were right.
I just did whatever I wanted, like always.
It's different!
You were just desperately
trying to protect Griffith.
But I didn't understand that...
So...
I mean...
I'm sorry.
Midland's troops were like ants attacking me.
I completely defeated them.
So did you confirm that
they were totally destroyed?
Of course I did, General Boscone!
You buffoon!
They are alive, and they occupy the supply base!
H-How could it be?
Get lost!
Waste no time in undoing
this disgrace to the empire!
Y-Yes, sir!
Calm down.
Governor Gennon...
The loss of a supply base
changes nothing in the overall war.
However, we must inflict
a crushing defeat on those insects.
Especially the impertinent Band of the Hawk...
Band of the Hawk?
What's wrong?
Never mind...
Leave it to them?
Yes, I will trust them with
our next offensive's siege.
Excuse me, Your Majesty...
...but can we charge such boorish
troops with so important a mission?
I agree with him.
My army would lead
the offensive if we were allowed...
Could I count on you?
Do you have perfect
confidence in your ability to win?
My intentions will not change.
Send word to Griffith.
When the preparations are finished,
they will take the field immediately.
Of course!
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...